

UX Researcher + Designer New York, NY janepark.me linkedin/in/janepark7 janeparkjp@gmail.com

I am a UX Researcher (with some design skills) who identifies problems, strategies, and solutions to help deliver meaningful user experiences that create a social impact in our society. I am grounded in my previous hospitality and education experiences, where listening and learning from real people is always the first step to success.

EXPERIENCE

Workshop In Business Opportunities (WIBO) — UX Designer + Researcher

MARCH 2019 - MAY 2019

- Conducted end-to-end research studies, including [planning, recruiting], interviews/ usability testing, synthesis, and communicating findings and recommendations
- Managed a team by delegating weekly tasks, meeting deadlines, and organized weekly meetings
- Translated research insights into solutions by creating wireframes and low-fidelity mockups

Upside Health — *Freelance UX Designer*

APRIL 2019

- Analyzed existing data and secondary research to inform design direction
- Collaborated with CEO and Head of Product to create a new feature for their product,
 Ouchie, for tracking pain management and history
- Designed and created the new interface for the feature (currently in development)

New York Code + Design Academy — Teaching Assistant

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2019

- Coached and mentored students on project work
- Advised on best practices and implementation of user research methods
- Graded assignments and helped troubleshoot students' development work

Multiple NYC Bakeries & Restaurants - Pastry Cook to Pastry Sous Chef

SEPTEMBER 2011 - MAY 2016

EDUCATION

BeginEx | UX Design Accelerated Program

New York Code + Design Academy | UX Design, Web Development Intensive State University of New York at New Paltz | BA, Psychology University of Huddersfield, UK | Study Abroad Psychology Program Robert McKee's Storytelling Seminar | 3 Day Seminar on the craft of Storytelling

SKILLS

Data synthesization

Information architecture

Interviews

Persona

Storytelling

Card sorting

Wireframing

Prototyping

Competitive analysis

Usability testing

User flows

TOOLS

Sketch

Figma

Balsamiq

InVision

Marvel

Zeplin

Trello

DEVELOPMENT

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

VOLUNTEER

DesignOps Summit '18

HACKATHONS

HexHacks 11/2018

BeginEx Design

Hackathon 3/2019